{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Exterior Trim Installation Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40415/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40415,"taskName":"Exterior Trim - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Exterior Trim","xmTaskDescriptor":"Exterior Trim Installation Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":5216,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Exterior siding Trim concrete window","textMessagingName":"Inst Exterior Trim","rolloverLongDesc":"Many homeowners choose to replace their wood trim with vinyl, aluminum \u0026 steel alternatives.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes fascia, soffits \u0026 trim around doors \u0026 windows.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Exterior Trim.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Exterior Trim Installation - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Door, Window \u0026 Roof Trim","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":69,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Exterior Trim Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Exterior Trim - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Exterior Trim Project","urlName":"Exterior-Trim-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Exterior Trim Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Door, Window \u0026 Roof Trim","searchKeywords":"trim, fascia, soffits, vinyl, wood, steel, aluminum","emcCategoryOid":-12064,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":707,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40415/":{"taskOID":40415,"originalTaskOID":40415,"setID":707,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6829,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200640,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install or completely replace exterior trim","answerDisplayText":"Install or completely replace exterior trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200641,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair or partially replace exterior trim","answerDisplayText":"Repair or partially replace exterior trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5054,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Trim","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of material will be used for trim? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":772,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum wrap","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum wrap","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2424,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fiber cement","answerDisplayText":"Fiber cement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5725,"questionDisplayText":"Water Damage or Rot on Existing Trim","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is there evidence of water damage or rot on existing wood trim?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5057,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Stories","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4367,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One","answerDisplayText":"One","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6545,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two","answerDisplayText":"Two","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6330,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three","answerDisplayText":"Three","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3947,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than three","answerDisplayText":"More than three","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5058,"questionDisplayText":"Current siding","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of sidiing do you currently have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7080,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood panel","answerDisplayText":"Wood panel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7055,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood Shingle","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shingle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":855,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Asbestos","answerDisplayText":"Asbestos","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6829,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200640,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install or completely replace exterior trim","answerDisplayText":"Install or completely replace exterior trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200641,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair or partially replace exterior trim","answerDisplayText":"Repair or partially replace exterior trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200640,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install or completely replace exterior trim","answerDisplayText":"Install or completely replace exterior trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200641,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair or partially replace exterior trim","answerDisplayText":"Repair or partially replace exterior trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5054,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Trim","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of material will be used for trim? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":772,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum wrap","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum wrap","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2424,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fiber cement","answerDisplayText":"Fiber cement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":772,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum wrap","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum wrap","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2424,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fiber cement","answerDisplayText":"Fiber cement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5725,"questionDisplayText":"Water Damage or Rot on Existing Trim","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is there evidence of water damage or rot on existing wood trim?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5057,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Stories","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4367,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One","answerDisplayText":"One","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6545,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two","answerDisplayText":"Two","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6330,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three","answerDisplayText":"Three","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3947,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than three","answerDisplayText":"More than three","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4367,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One","answerDisplayText":"One","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6545,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two","answerDisplayText":"Two","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6330,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three","answerDisplayText":"Three","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3947,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than three","answerDisplayText":"More than three","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5058,"questionDisplayText":"Current siding","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of sidiing do you currently have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7080,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood panel","answerDisplayText":"Wood panel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7055,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood Shingle","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shingle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":855,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Asbestos","answerDisplayText":"Asbestos","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7080,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood panel","answerDisplayText":"Wood panel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7055,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood Shingle","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shingle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":855,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Asbestos","answerDisplayText":"Asbestos","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}